linkluv.co 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy | LinkLuvLinkLuv

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the website that linked you here. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy on this website. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of current practices, as they may change in the future.

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. Similarly, we need you to provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted and use our website and related services. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, we will not be able to contact you and you will not be able to use our website or services.

The personal information we collect from members includes name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, user name, and password. We also collect payment information from members, including without limitation the name on your card, card number, expiration date, card security code, card type, and card billing information.

We use the information that we collect to provide our services, to contact you regarding our products and services, and to improve our site. We also use this information—directly, indirectly, and in combination with data we exchange with other parties—to introduce you to informational, service, and/or product offerings of our marketing partners, select unaffiliated companies, unaffiliated list brokers, affiliate marketers, and companies that want you to receive their advertising messages. (collectively, “Other Companies”). We do this by using your personal information so we can present you with these offers, and also by transferring, licensing, and/or sharing your personal information with Other Companies. We hope you will be interested in the marketing materials and promotions with which you are presented. We do not use the personal information submitted by attendees in any other way. Once a third-party obtains your personal information, its subsequent use is controlled by their business practices, which is beyond our control. By providing us an email address, you are expressly consenting to being contacted by anyone to whom we subsequently share or transfer your personal information.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to, and members of, the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide.

Anything you send us, post on our site, or use with our service, such as emails or voice recordings, or if other users or third parties send us anything about your activities or postings, we will collect such information into a file specific to you. We use information in the file that we maintain for you, and other information that we obtain from your use of the services, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our membership agreements.

We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Additionally, we share and/or transfer your personal information only in the ways set forth in this privacy policy.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

LinkLuv, LLC 2885 Sanford Ave SW #27497 Grandville, MI 49418 (302) 439-0841  

This privacy policy is effective as of July 5, 2013.
